[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
In this module, we talked about how to do regression part.
在这一部分,  我们来讨论如果做回归分析
We talked about how to use it to predict house prices.
我们将学习如何利用回归分析来预测房价
Now, we're going to build together and pricing notebook using Python to predict
今天， 我们将使用python， 一起建立一个IPython Notebook来预测房价
house prices for a real dataset, based on what's called King County data.
房价信息来自一个真实数据集,  我们叫它 '国王郡数据' (King County data)
King County is the county or the region where the city of Seattle, where Emmy and
'国王郡' 是美国西雅图所在区域的一个县
I live, is located.
我和艾米就住在那里
So, we're going to take some of the data, it's public record data, and
接下来,  我们将使用这个公共数据集的一些数据
actually build together a regression notebook to predict house prices.
一起来建立一个 回归notebook 来预测房价
So let's get started.
现在我们进入正题
Okay, so here's a blank IPython notebook.
现在我们这里有一个空的IPython  Notebook
And just to start, what I'm going to do is hide the,
我们已经打开这个notebook 接下来有要做的是
first let's change the title, so we're going to
首先改Notebook的标题
change the title to predicting house prices.
我们把Notebook名字改成 ‘预测房价’ (predicting house prices)
So we just renamed it, and I like to the view menu and hide the header,
重命名以后 我到菜单的 'View' 选项，选择隐藏了页眉和工具栏
and the toolbar, this part on the bottom, so we have more space on the slide.
就是底下这部分 这样  我们就有足够空间
So we done the hiding.
好 现在我们完成了隐藏
And the first thing we're going to do is fire up Graph Lab Create,
接下来我们要做的第一件事情就是 激活Graph Lab Create
the tool that we're going to use to run some algorithms in Python.
使用这个工具  我们可以在Python中运行机器学习算法
So I'm going to type ask M, and
我现在添加注解:
I'm going to say fire up graphlab create.
"激活Graph Lab Create"
So we do that by typing import graphlab.
我们通过输入import Graphlab来激活
And that just starts up graphlab create.
目前 我们只是开启了GraphLab Create
Now our task today is to predict house prices.
我们今天的任务是 预测房价
So the first thing that we are going to do is to load some
所以接下来首先要做的是 导入一些房价信息的数据
house sales data.
导入一些房价信息的数据
So this is public data, public record, of house that got sold in the Seattle region.
这是一个公共数据集 记录了在西雅图区域被售出房子的情况
So, I'm going to call this table data sales,
现在我们把这个表格命名为 "销售数据" (data sales)
and I'm going to say graphlab .SFrame.
然后建立graphlab .SFrame.
Remember we talked about SFrame as the data structure for
还记得吗 我们讲过 SFrame是一种数据结构
representing tabular data in graphlab create?
它在Graph Lab Create中被用来表示单元数据
So it's a really fast hour of core data structure, and
所以它的确是我们的核心数据结构
we're going to load up some house things in there.
好 我们现在就准备导入一些房子的相关信息
So this is going to be called home underscore data,
所以，我们把它叫做 "家庭_数据" (home_data)
and notice that data is now complete for you, so that just happened then.
注意，IPython Notebook 完全为我们做了很多事情, 所以接下来我们可以看到:
So if I just type while this is loading up and it's firing up GraphLab Create,
我仅仅键入简单命令，就可以导入数据，并开启GraphLab Create
if I just type sales here, you'll see what that data looks like.
例如，我只是在这里输入‘sales'  你将会看到数据是这个样子
So I'm going to scroll up a little bit to the top, I just type sales and says,
我向上滚动一点儿  输入'sales'
there was an ID for a date with the sale, the price, number of bedrooms,
我们可以看到，对于一个日期，存在一个唯一标识符 (ID) 其后包含房子销售日期 价格  卧室数量 面积
number of bathrooms, square feet, which is kind of like that American version of
看起来是美国模式的
square meters if you're living in other countries, for the house, feet for
假如你住在其他国家 对于房子来说
the lot of land, number of floors, in a bunch of the categories.
还会有土地英尺数 楼层等很多不同的分类
Whether the house has a view or not, whether it sits on a grade,
房子是否有观景台, 是否建在台阶上，这意味着房子在一个小山上
which means it's on a hill, and a bunch of other measurements.
这意味着房子在一个小山上  另外还有很多其他各种房子相关的衡量标准
We've loaded this house data and it looks pretty cool.
我们已经导入了一些关于房子的数据 看起来相当不错哦
The first thing that we're going to do is use graph lab canvas and
我们首先要做的是 使用Graph Lab的canvas
do a little bit of visualization.
来做一些可视化
So what I'm going to do is again, create the cell.
所以我们要再来生成一个新的模块
And this says exploring the data for housing.
我们注释为: 探索房子售价相关数据
So housing sales.
我们要做的是: 探索房子售价相关数据
So we're going to do some data exploration.
所以我们将做一些数据探索工作
So we're going to take the sales data and I'm going to show, so
我们将获得房子销售数据 然后把他们展示出来
when I type .show, it's going to show some visualization of that data,
当我们输入'show',  程序将会自动进行数据可视化
and in particular, what I'm going to do is view,
特别是  如果我们输入'view'
just rather than letting graphlab do this view, we're going
就不仅仅是让graphlab展示数据 而是
to just do a scatter plot, so we'll see what a scatter plot is in a second.
绘制一个散点图 我们马上就可以看到效果了
We'll just type new scatter plot that relates two variables.
我们现在输入 ‘new scatter plot’ 它有两个相关变量
On the X axis, we're going to have the square feet of living space.
x-轴被用来表示居住面积
And in the y axis, we're going to put the price.
y-轴被用来表示房价
So, what that should show us,
接下来 应该呈现给我们的是
is the relationship to where square feet of living space and price.
一个散点图来展示居住面积和房价之间的关系
Now, one little trick that I like to do when I create notebooks
在生成Notebook时候 我有一个小技巧
is that sometimes you push out graph lab canvas in a new tub, but
有时候你要在一个新的tub中推出graphlab 但是呢
also it's kind of fun to just plot those scatter plots and simple plots
如果我们把这些散点图和简单的曲线图绘制在notebook内部 也不错
inside the notebook itself, so it can print it off and hand it off to somebody.
这样 对于其他人 我们就省去了打印并且让别人也可以看到
So the way to do that is I can just tell graph lab canvas to set its target,
唯一解决办法是我们手动设置graph lab canvas的目标(target)
not to be the browser which is the default target,
不要把浏览器设置为默认目标
but to be the ipython notebook.
而是把IPython notebook设置为默认目标
I just type canvas.set_target('ipynb'), ipython notebook, and
我刚刚输入了 canvas.set_target('ipynb'), 来完成设置目标任务
it's going to plot this scatter plot on the notebook itself.
然后散点图就会被绘制显示在notebook内部
So if I hit enter here, what's going to do is take
如果我们点击这里
those two axes and just plot them together.
会考虑两个轴 然后一起绘制
So here we go.
接下来
On the X axis is the square feet of the house, and the Y axis is the price.
在x-轴 是房子面积  y-轴为房价
So let's kind of browse this a little bit.
好 让我们接下来再多看一些东西
So for example, the more square feet they're big houses, so
例如 更大居住面积的房子
if I mouse over here you'll see that this big house had 5,990 square feet,
如果我们把鼠标移动到这里 我们可以看到 这个大房子有5990平方英尺
which is pretty big, that's like 600 square meters,
真的是挺大的  相当于大约600平方米
and it was sold for $2.2 million, which is quite a lot of money.
它的售价为220万美元 一笔大数目啊
Now, you also notice there's a nice relationship,
现在 你应该也注意到了这些关系
that the bigger houses tend to cost more.
大房子常常售价更高
There's a big blob of houses here, so
这一块聚集了大量的房子
most houses are between 1,000 and 3,000 square feet.
大多数面积在1000-3000平方英尺之间
And even at this level, see this house over here, it's an outlier.
甚至在这个纵轴上  看这个房子 这是一个异常值
So even though it's only 1,910 square feet, it was sold for $1.5 million.
即使只有1910平方英尺, 也要1百50万
Well, down here there's a house that is similar 1,700 square feet,
往下面看 这个房子  大概1700平方英尺
that sold for just $149,000.
要卖14.9万美元
This is a big discrepancy.
不同房子  售价存在巨大差异
And here's the biggest outlier of the dataset.
这里有一个数据集中的异常值
This house has 3,730 square feet and got sold for $2.5 million.
这个房子3730平方英尺 售价为2百50万
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community